{
    "categories": [
        "Video-Games",
        "Movies",
        "Nature",
        "Maths",
        "Computer-Science",
        "Geography",
        "Music",
        "History",
        "Science"
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What was Mario from Super Mario Bros. original name?",
            "answer": "Jumpman",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What was the forest area from Super Mario World called?",
            "answer": "Forest of Illusion",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What was the second Ratchet and Clank game called in the UK? [Hint: Ratchet and Clank: <???>]",
            "answer": "Locked and Loaded",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
            "answer": "4",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What's the derivate of e?",
            "answer": "e",
            "author": "Forces Unknown"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What is the capital city of England?",
            "answer": "London",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What USA state will you find the city of Orlando?",
            "answer": "Florida",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What type is the pok√©mon bidoof?",
            "answer": "Normal",
            "author": "202103129330810880"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What type of Pokemon is Weedle?",
            "answer": "bug",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What was the city of Istanbul called before 1930?",
            "answer": "Constantinople",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What is the capital city of France?",
            "answer": "Paris",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Computer-Science",
            "question": "Who was the original creator of C++?",
            "answer": "Bjarne Stroustrup",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "Who was the director of the 1997 film 'Titanic'?",
            "answer": "James Cameron",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What is the most famous game by Bay12Games?",
            "answer": "Dwarf Fortress",
            "author": "202103129330810880"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Nature",
            "question": "What is a group of lions called? [1 word]",
            "answer": "Pride",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "Who was the lead game designer of Skyrim?",
            "answer": "Todd Howard",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "What was the first Star Wars movie released? Hint: Star Wars: <your answer here>",
            "answer": "A New Hope",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Computer-Science",
            "question": "What language is C++ a superset of?",
            "answer": "C",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "Which country lies on the border between Spain and France?",
            "answer": "Andorra",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Computer-Science",
            "question": "What does USB stand for?",
            "answer": "Universal Serial Bus",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is square root of -1?",
            "answer": "i"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Nature",
            "question": "How many legs do all insects have?",
            "answer": "6",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Nature",
            "question": "What is the only type of bird which has the ability to fly backwards?",
            "answer": "hummingbird",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Nature",
            "question": "What shape is a goats pupil?",
            "answer": "rectangle",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "How many stars are on the Paramount studio logo?",
            "answer": "22",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What is the capital city of Japan?",
            "answer": "Tokyo",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "In Minecraft, what is the surface block of the Mushroom biome?",
            "answer": "Mycelium",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is the seventh number of the Fibbonacci sequence?",
            "answer": "13",
            "author": "231104432102834176"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What is the tallest mountain in Skyrim? [4 words]",
            "answer": "Throat of the World",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Computer-Science",
            "question": "A NOR gate is considered a universal gates; What is the other universal gate?",
            "answer": "NAND",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is 9 squared?",
            "answer": "81",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is the square root of 144?",
            "answer": "12",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "In what city will you find the Burj Khalifa?",
            "answer": "Dubai",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What is the westernmost country in Europe?",
            "answer": "Iceland",
            "author": "231104432102834176"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What is the only game from the Mother/Earthbound series that hasn't yet been brought to the US?",
            "answer": "Mother 3",
            "author": "343644106569940994"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What is the most commonly spoken language in the world?",
            "answer": "Chinese",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What is the longest river in the world?",
            "answer": "Amazon",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Nature",
            "question": "What trees do acorns grow on?",
            "answer": "Oak",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What is the largest country in the world in terms of surface area?",
            "answer": "Russia",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What shape is at the center of the national flag of Japan?",
            "answer": "Circle",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Computer-Science",
            "question": "Who is credited for breaking the Nazi's ciphers via the use of the Enigma Machine?",
            "answer": "Alan Turing",
            "author": "150049709698973696"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "In which USA state is Mount Rushmore located?",
            "answer": "South Dakota",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "Which sea borders the south of France?",
            "answer": "Mediterranean",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "In which USA state is Area 51 located?",
            "answer": "Nevada",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "Who created the monster in the movie 'Frankenstein'?",
            "answer": "Dr Frankenstein",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Nature",
            "question": "What is the temperature to which all particles freeze?",
            "answer": "-273.15",
            "author": "343644106569940994"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "What was the maiden name of Harry Potter's mother?",
            "answer": "Lily",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "What was the name of the main antagonist from the horror film 'Sinister'?",
            "answer": "Bughuul",
            "author": "343644106569940994"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What is the largest island in the Caribbean?",
            "answer": "Cuba",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Nature",
            "question": "What is the fastest fish in the ocean?",
            "answer": "Sailfish",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "In 'Mean Girls', what continent did Cady Heron live in before moving to the USA?",
            "answer": "Africa",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "What is Darth Vader's real name?",
            "answer": "Anakin Skywalker",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "In what region of Tamriel is the game TES: Oblivion set?",
            "answer": "cyrodiil",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "Which emoji did Patrick Stewart voice in the emoji movie?",
            "answer": "üí©",
            "author": "145945481825091584"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Music",
            "question": "Who is the drummer from the band TooL?",
            "answer": "Danny Carrey",
            "author": "343644106569940994"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is the square root of - 1",
            "answer": "i",
            "author": "145945481825091584"
        },
        {
            "cat": "History",
            "question": "What year did World War Two end?",
            "answer": "1945",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Computer-Science",
            "question": "Who is most usually credited for coming up with the fast inverse square root algorithm?",
            "answer": "John Carmack",
            "author": "221609129347645442"
        },
        {
            "cat": "History",
            "question": "What year did World War Two begin?",
            "answer": "1939",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "History",
            "question": "What year did Harold get an arrow in his eye?",
            "answer": "1066",
            "author": "145945481825091584"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Science",
            "question": "What is 2nd planet from the sun?",
            "answer": "Venus",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Science",
            "question": "What will you find inbetween Mars and Jupiter?",
            "answer": "asteroid Belt",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Science",
            "question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell?",
            "answer": "mitochondria",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Music",
            "question": "What is the abreviattion to the industrial metal band 'Nine Inch Nails'?",
            "answer": "NIN",
            "author": "343644106569940994"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What does RYNO stand for in the Ratchet and Clank series?",
            "answer": "Rip Ya A New One",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "Who invented Fermat's last theorem",
            "answer": "Fermat",
            "author": "237264833433567233"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is 9 + 10 * 2?",
            "answer": "29",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is a^2+b^2=c^2 known as?",
            "answer": "pythagoras theorem",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is 101b2 + 100b2?",
            "answer": "1001b2",
            "author": "340661564556312591"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "Who created Stardew Valley all by himself?",
            "answer": "Eric Barone",
            "author": "343644106569940994"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is 5 + 5?",
            "answer": "10",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "History",
            "question": "The cold war ended with the death of which infamous leader?",
            "answer": "Joseph Stalin",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "Which country in the UK does not appear on the flag of the Union Jack?",
            "answer": "Wales",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "Which movie is the famous quote 'Houston, we have a problem' from?",
            "answer": "Apollo 13",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What is the capital city of the USA state of New York?",
            "answer": "Albany",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is 5 + 10?",
            "answer": "15",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Music",
            "question": "Complete the lyric's missing space: 'I, hurt myself today, to see if I still __'",
            "answer": "feel",
            "author": "343644106569940994"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "How many numbers from 1 to 333 contain a 2?",
            "answer": "151",
            "author": "237264833433567233"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "How many prime numbers are there between 1 and 100?",
            "answer": "25",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "How many digits does the number 2^30 have?",
            "answer": "10",
            "author": "293835615513083918"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "How many zeros does a Googol have?",
            "answer": "100",
            "author": "343644106569940994"
        },
        {
            "cat": "History",
            "question": "Which state did the USA purchase from Russia in 1867?",
            "answer": "Alaska",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Science",
            "question": "What is the greeting of Vsauce in his videos?",
            "answer": "Hey, Vsauce, Michael here",
            "author": "293835615513083918"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "In alphabetical order, which 4 USA states border Mexico?(Answer like: State1 State2 State3 State4",
            "answer": "Arizona California New Mexico Texas",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "History",
            "question": "The period of European history that lasted from the 14th to the the 17th century is known as the...?",
            "answer": "Renaissance",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Music",
            "question": "What was the most controversial movie the band Nine Inch Nails created?",
            "answer": "The Broken Movie",
            "author": "343644106569940994"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Science",
            "question": "Which one mostly transports blood with much oxygen: Arteries or veins?",
            "answer": "Arteries",
            "author": "293835615513083918"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Music",
            "question": "What artist was known for composing DOOM (2016)'s soundtrack",
            "answer": "Mick Gordon",
            "author": "343644106569940994"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What country borders the south of USA?",
            "answer": "Mexico",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "In which ocean will you find the mariana trench?",
            "answer": "pacific",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Science",
            "question": "How many manned missions landed on the moon?",
            "answer": "6",
            "author": "231104432102834176"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "What was the subtitle of the first Harry Potter movie in the UK? Harry Poterr and the...",
            "answer": "Philosopher's Stone",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Music",
            "question": "How many strings does a bass guitar have?",
            "answer": "4",
            "author": "293835615513083918"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "In the Harry Potter universe, what name is given to non-magic people?",
            "answer": "Muggle",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "What are the different worlds called in Inception?",
            "answer": "dream layers",
            "author": "293835615513083918"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Science",
            "question": "In what year was *the general theory of relativity* published?",
            "answer": "1915",
            "author": "231104432102834176"
        },
        {
            "cat": "History",
            "question": "What year was The Great Fire of London?",
            "answer": "1666",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Science",
            "question": "How many biceps muscles does a human have?",
            "answer": "4",
            "author": "293835615513083918"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What is the creator of Minecraft's real name?",
            "answer": "Markus Persson",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is 30/(1/2) + 10?",
            "answer": "70",
            "author": "293835615513083918"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Computer-Science",
            "question": "What is a pointer technically?",
            "answer": "Integer",
            "author": "293835615513083918"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Nature",
            "question": "What tree type would you find apples on?",
            "answer": "Apple",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What is Mario, from Super Mario Bro's, real job?",
            "answer": "Plumber",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Nature",
            "question": "What kind of verebrate is a dolphin?",
            "answer": "Mammal",
            "author": "293835615513083918"
        }
    ]
}